This is number one [music] of three of
my favorite e-devices. So, the first one
is my e-reader, the Boox Palma.
>> [music]
>> So, I've been using this for 3 years now
and it's my favorite way to read books.
So, one of the reasons I like the Boox
Palma is because it runs [music]
Android, and so it means that you can
really customize it however you want and
install any apps that you want. Probably
the bigger reason and the initial reason
why I switched to this one is because of
the form [music] factor. So, unlike a
traditional e-reader, it's kind of
bulky, so it's kind of like the size of
a book. And this one is a phone form
factor, so it's really nice to hold. It
really helps me read more often because
it's just easier to use and it's a form
factor that I'm used to. If you compare
the experience of reading a [music] book
on your phone compared to reading a book
on this, it's just way nicer to read on
this, and I can actually read books for
several hours on this, like especially
if I'm on a train or an airplane versus
my phone. In the past, I've also used
this device as a dopamine detox device.
When I don't want to bring my phone out,
I can just bring this [music] and still
have access to messaging apps, AI apps,
or maps. And depending on the version
you get, you can also get a SIM card to
get data on this.